functionalauditing.com 2011-10-22

# Functional Auditing - Privacy Policy

We at Functional Auditing Limited, are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect from you to confidentially personalize your Personal Values and holistic Functioning in accordance with your true Inner Potential. We only sell, trade or rent your personal information to other parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy and your acceptance of indemnity.

Please read all the details in our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to users of the Functional Auditing  and Functional Audit.com web sites, and applies to all sites on the Functional Auditing domain namely www.functional auditing.  All information collected, will be protected to the best of our ability and the choices you have concerning your Personal Information are described within this policy. The Functionalaudit.com is controlled by Functional Auditing Limited, located at

108L Colwill Road

By using Functional Auditing Limited website you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also applies to users that have agreed to receive e-mails, marketing material, Reports or any other material from Functional Auditing Limited and or any joint marketing "Advertisers".

All Advertisers that collaborate with Functionalauditing.com or Functionalaudit.com, whether at Functional Auditing Limited, via email, on third party websites, via co-registration or otherwise.

I. Collectable Information  
2\. The Use Of Collectable Information  
3\. Information Sharing and Disclosure  
4\. Third Parties  
5\. Security  
6\. Accessing and Updating Personal Information  
7\. Data Integrity  
8\. Children  
9\. Opt Out Options.

Functional Auditing Limited regularly review our compliance with this Policy. We may edit this Policy from time to time should we find it necessary. Should we make any substantial involving the use of any Personal Information, we would notify you by both e-mailing and posting a prominent notice on our privacy policy, as well as an indicator on the home page of www.functionalauditing.com. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy via email to contactus@functionalaudit.com, or via postal mail to 1B Limmer Place, Browns Bay, Auckland 0632 New Zealand.  Once we have receive any formal written complaints at this address, it is our policy to contact the complainant regarding his or her concerns regarding their Personal audit or any other relevant information.

**Registration:** Registration is required to participate in the Functional Audit, or in any promotion or competition that may be run by Functional Auditing Limited. You will be asked for Personal information as part of the registration process. Functionalaudit's minimum age for the use of the assessments must be 16 years or older, without exception and it is not Functional auditing's responsibility to verify such ages.  Upon registration the following information would be essential Full Name, email address, telephone number, street address, home town, country and postal code.

**Additional Personal Information** : will be collected through use of the site including all audits through responses to questions, or through various offers that may be provided on site from time to time. Functional Auditing Limited may collect and retain Personal Information relating to email marketing sent to, and opened by, employers, teachers, parents or relevant Government authority from what soever cause arising out of the use of the Functional Audit  orthe Functionalaudit.com website.

**Other Information** : In addition to private information, additional information may be collected, such as system information, browser type (e.g., Mozilla Fox, Internet Explorer), or IP addresses, the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), what version of Adobe Flash you are using (e.g., Flash 9.0), CPU type (e.g. Pentium), your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access), information about your geographic location, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We also track some of the pages that you visit on our Website through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). This tracks usage information about users who have received targeted promotional campaigns. In addition, Functional Auditing Limited uses third-party service provider or partners to employ anonymous cookies for accounting and data integrity purposes.

Other sources: We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly available information or information available from third party sources, such as updated delivery and address information from our carriers or third parties, and add it to our account information, generally for updating purposes. We may also obtain information about you through optional co-registration and/or advertisements on sites operated by third parties.

Cookies: Cookies are pieces of data stored in the browser's memory or written to the user's hard drive that provide the ability to recall information across user sessions. This also enables tracking of various user actions and helps customize the display of site content and personalized advertisements. Most web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. You do not have to accept cookies to use Quiz Rocket, but Quiz Rocket may not work correctly if cookies are disabled, and some functionality may be completely unavailable. You may reset your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to reject cookies generally. The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable cookies altogether.

We at Functional Auditing Limited do not intentionally try and store cookies or invade your privacy, However, please be aware due to various software applications the storing of cookies might take place.

**Marketing** :  
a)  Personal Information that you may submit to Functional Auditing limited  remains your property, but by submitting your personal information, you grant Functional auditing Limited the right to use that information for reference or training purposes only. Any Personal Information such as your Personal Particulars (eg Name, address, e-mail address, phone number, etc would be omitted from that information pertaining to the assessment outcomes via a report.

  B)  Delivering certain direct marketing offers to you via telemarketing, e-mail marketing, direct mail, SMS messaging and other types of direct marketing.

Your Personal Information may be used in a variety of other ways, including:

* Ensuring better presentation of site content to match demographic interests.  
* Customizing the website [in accordance with Functional Auditing Limited upgrading necessities]  
* Improving the web site  
* Contacting you regarding Functionalaudit.com (including your registration with Functionalaudit.com or associated companies  
* Fulfilling Reporting Requirements  
* Tracking compliance with Functionalaudits indemnity Rules  
* Improving content and feedback purposes  
* Confirming user registration with Functionalaudit.com or Associate companies.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We only share Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of Functionalauditing's  domain in the following limited circumstances:

**Third Party Service-Providers** : Functional Auditing Limited may from time to time unintentionally share Personal Information should we be updating our websites via third parties who may be contracted to do such Upgrades of our website. All these third parties would be bound by non disclosure agreements, however in the unlikely event that such information is passed on without our knowledge such circumstances would be out of the control of Functional Auditing Limited's domain, and it must be understood that Functional Auditing Limited does not accept any responsibility or accountability from whatsoever cause arising out of the personal information be utilized for whatsoever cause by such third parties.

**Other Third Parties** : We may sell your Personal Information to your employers, recruitment agencies, schools or other social groups should it be deemed necessary,  should the audit be of such a nature, that it may be  required by such third parties in order to establish your true functionality, dysfunctionality, Personal Values, Leadership Qualities for which that third party would be responsible for your behavior within their environment. Non of your personal Information would be disclosed without you accepting our terms and conditions agreed before starting the assessment.

**Indeminity;  ** _Functional Auditing Limited ** _ _** and any other related party_:   We reserve the right to access, use, preserve or disclose personal information: as required by law , regulation, legal process or governmental request and when we believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure is necessary to protect our or our users' rights, property or safety and / or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, legal process or governmental request served upon our company; enforce the terms and conditions of Functional Auditing Limited, including investigation of potential violations; and to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information:**   Functional Auditing Limited may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about our user database with Partners, Promoters and Affiliates which could include demographics, usage, or characteristics of Functional Auditing Limited's participation as a group. We may also share with Promoters usage information about users who have utilized our services or assessments for the purpose of formatting future training or marketing campaigns and or upgrading user information used in reporting statistics. This information could be collected by the tracking of some pages you may visit on Functional Auditing Limited's or affiliated websites through the use of pixel tags.

**Merger/Acquisitions** : If Functional Auditing Limited becomes involved in any merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will not be responsible for ensuring that you are notified that your Personal Information is transferred. However, Functional Auditing Limited will do everything reasonable possible to notify you of such Merger or Acquisition.

If you provide us with your address, telephone number and/or email, you may receive occasional mailings, phone calls, or emails from us or our agents with information on Functional Auditing Limited's new products, industry news, product features, and upcoming events. We send promotional email to our users, including users who have registered to do assessments but did not complete them.

To the extent we use Personal Information to email you about our products and services, noting that all our email practices are in compliance with the relevant countries spam laws.

If you do not wish to receive promotional communications from us, please unsubscribe by sending us an e-mail informing us that you no longer desire any further promotional emails you may receive from us or you can also contact us by contacting us via our web page "Contact Us" and submit your cancellation request.

If you do not wish to receive personalized advertising from us, please contact us now by our "Contact Us" web page at www.functionalauditing.com or at our postal address as disclosed on our website under "About US" .

Functional Auditing Limited includes third party advertising and links to other websites. These third party websites and advertisers, or internet advertising companies working on their behalf, may deliver to your web browser many of the advertisements you see when you use theWebsite. They may also use cookies, Javascript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs) and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisement and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features they may use, and the privacy practices of these entities are not covered by this Policy. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices.   
If you want to prevent a third-party ad server and/or third-party service provider from sending and reading cookies on your computer or using any of the other features referred to above, currently you must visit each ad network's and service provider's website individually and opt out (if they offer this capability). Note that disabling cookies may limit, or in some cases, preclude your use of this site.

Please remember that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by us at Functional Auditing Limited and the Functionalaudit.com website. On the functionalauditing.com and the functionalaudit.com or within messages received from the Functionalauditing.com or the the functionalaudit.com websites there may be embedded codes or links to other third party websites (including Advertisers) that have different privacy and security policies. Functional Auditing Limited does not endorse, nor is Functional Auditing limited responsible for the accuracy of these policies. The entities which advertise and/or place banner ads on Functional Auditing website including co-registration advertisers are independent third parties and are not affiliated with Functional Auditing limited in any way.  You should consult these third party sites for their policies.

  **Security.**

Functional Auditing Limited has security measures in place to protect information against unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure, including a comprehensive information security program. Functional Auditing Limited uses standard industry procedures and guidelines. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store your Personal Information.

Functional Auditing Limited  also ensures that all third parties who receive Personal Information have in place reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information, to protect it from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure and that third party service providers maintain information security practices and programs in accordance with applicable law.

We restrict access to Personal Information through User names and passwords to: key executives of Functional Auditing Limited and relevant members of the development team (including employees, contractors and agents of Functional Auditing Limited) who have direct access to information under our control, who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our products and services; or persons who need to comply with record retention requirements by law. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations.

Personal information collected by Functional Auditing Limited are stored in our system normally for a period of one year for administration purposes before being deleted automatically.  
However such information could be deleted at any time. Should there be any loss of information from whatsoever cause, Functional Auditing Limited is not responsible for such loss or action.

Please contact us if you would like to access your Personal Information that  we have collected about you. We will in good faith make the effort to provide you with access to your Personal Information however you may access that information by using your User Name and Password when registering to do an audit.

  **Data integrity**

We process Personal Information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on you to update or correct your personal information whenever necessary.

**Children** Functional Auditing Limited does not knowingly collect personal information from minors under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 16, please do not provide us with your personal information. If you have reason to believe that a child has provided us with their personal information, please contact us at the address given above and we will delete that information from our databases.

Users under 16 years of age are not allowed to participate in our Audits that are offered by Functional Auditing Limited. Functional Auditing  does not hold themselves and are not responsible for any information obtained from underage users who have provided false information regarding their age. However, in these instances parents may visit the Functional Auditing.com -  "Contact Us" page and request the child's personal information be removed. Functional Auditing Limited  is not responsible for any offers presented to underage users who have provided through false information regarding their age.

Parents must contact our service providers directly. No information should be submitted or registered by users under 16 years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By Clicking the button accept when registering on the website it is clearly understood that this Privacy Policy has been read and accepted.

Alternatively, you may send postal mail to the following address:  
 **Functional Auditing  Limited**

108L  Colwill Road  
Royal Heights  
Auckland 0614

New Zealand

Tel: 09 832 3941

Contact Us

Updated on 1st August 2011
